[
  {
    "id": "100",
    "qPrompt": "Dominica",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡²", "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡¬", "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡ª", "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡¿"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡²"
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "qPrompt": "Cook Islands",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡¹", "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡²", "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡°"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡°"
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "qPrompt": "North Korea",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡­", "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¾", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡ª", "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡µ"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡µ"
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "qPrompt": "Tanzania",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡­", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¿", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡°", "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¬"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¿"
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "qPrompt": "Argentina",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡©", "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡³", "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡«", "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡·"
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "qPrompt": "Panama",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡´", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¹", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡¬"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¦"
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "qPrompt": "Uzbekistan",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¿", "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¿", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡´", "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡°"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¿"
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "qPrompt": "Switzerland",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡·", "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡±", "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡­"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡­"
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "qPrompt": "Ireland",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡ª", "ğŸ‡»ğŸ‡¨", "ğŸ´ó §ó ¢ó ³ó £ó ´ó ¿"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡ª"
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "qPrompt": "Ukraine",
    "options": ["ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡¼", "ğŸ‡«ğŸ‡´", "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦", "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡ª"],
    "answer": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¦"
  }
]
